Hey hey everybody
嘿 嘿 亲爱的同学
We've got something to say
我们有话要讲
We may seem as different
我们看似不同
As the night is from day
像昼夜各一方
But if you look a little deeper
但若你细细观察
And you will see
便会发现真相
That I'm just like you
你和我一样
And you're just like me Yeah
我也像你那样
Hey hey everybody
嘿 嘿 同学们
we're here to shout
我们在这里大声宣告
That the magic of friendship is what
友谊的魔法
It's all about
是永恒的光芒
Yeah We thought they were different
曾以为彼此不同
As the night is from the day
如昼夜相隔千里
Until Twilight Sparkle helped to see another way
直到紫悦让我们心聚一起
So get up
来扬帆
get down
起航
If you're gonna come around
我们携手向远方
We can work together
我们同心协力
Helping Twilight win the crown
帮助紫悦赢得王冠
So get up
来扬帆
get down
起航
Cause it's gonna make a sound
这歌声传四方
If we work together
我们同心协力
Helping Twilight Sparkle win the crown
帮助紫悦夺回王冠
Hey hey
Hands up now
现在举起手
We're sending a message to the crowd
让大家听见我们的口号
Hands wave up
举过头
Then comes down
放至腰
We party together all around
派对时刻开始了
Generous honesty
慷慨 诚实
Laughter kindness loyalty
欢笑 善良 忠诚
Twilight helped us each to see
紫悦帮我们看清
All that we can be
我们的本性
So get up
来扬帆
Get down
起航
Cause it's gonna make a sound
嘹亮歌声传四方
If we work together
我们一起努力
Helping Twilight win the crown
帮助紫悦赢得王冠
So get up
来扬帆
Get down
起航
Cause it's gonna make a sound
这歌声传四方
If we work together
我们同心协力
Helping Twilight Sparkle win the crown
帮助紫悦夺回王冠
I'm gonna be myself
要做真实自己
No matter what I do
坚定不移
And if we're different Yeah
你我若有分歧
I want you to be true to you
就让心灵指引你
If you follow me
跟随我的脚步
We'll put our differences aside
抛开所有的分歧
We'll stick together and start working on that school pride
让我们一起努力 为校园荣耀努力
Jump up make a sound Hey
跃起 齐声喊 嘿
Stomp your hooves
跺跺脚
Turn around
转一转
Start now
现在开始
Make a change
做个改变
Gonna come around
旧貌换新貌
Jump up make a sound Hey
跃起 齐声喊 嘿
Stomp your hooves
跺跺脚
Turn around
转一转
Canterlot Wondercolts
坎特洛特奇骏队
Help her win the crown
请帮助她赢得王冠
Jump up
起跳
make a sound Hey
跃起 齐声喊 嘿
Stomp your hooves
跺跺脚
Turn around
转一转
Start now
现在开始
Make a change
做个改变
Gonna come around
旧貌换新貌
Jump up make a sound Hey
跃起 齐声喊 嘿
Stomp your hooves
跺跺脚
Turn around
转一转
Canterlot Wondercolts
坎特洛特奇骏队
Help her win the crown
请帮她夺冠
Jump up make a sound Hey
跃起 齐声喊 嘿
Stomp your hooves
跺跺脚
Turn around
转一转
Start now
现在开始
Make a change
做个改变
Gonna come around
旧貌换新貌
Jump up make a sound Hey
跃起 齐声喊 嘿
Stomp your hooves
跺跺脚
Turn around
转一转
给我摘下来